[{"answer": "Not on this I don't.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 6, "question": "Do you trust Ahmadinejad?", "qSentId": 5}, {"answer": "The idea that somehow making a business profitable is different than helping people is really a foreign idea.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 14, "question": "What if Mitt Romney isn't the best person?", "qSentId": 13}, {"answer": "IRK CAMERON, ACTOR: I think that it's -- it's -- it's unnatural.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 18, "question": "Do you think homosexuality is a sin?", "qSentId": 17}, {"answer": "No, I haven't.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Have you ever seen anything like this in your lifetime?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Well, let me tell you what's not vague, and that is five days after, five days after the what was very quickly determined by the intelligence committee as a terrorist attack, they trotted out our ambassador to the U.N. to every major news outlet saying that this was a spontaneous demonstration because of a hateful video.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Where do you think we are with this?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Are you in favor of that?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Harry Truman in his great reelection campaign when he was so far behind that Gallup quit taking polls in mid-September, went after Dewey, and the crowd would yell out give'em hell, Harry.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "And isn't it time now for you to accept that this negativity has pounded you into a position where much as you would like to keep it positive, isn't it time you got the old Gingrich fist out and gave Romney a good old smack?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Well, there is a real difference between a venture capitalist and a vulture capitalist.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "Because if Mitt Romney now wins the nomination, haven't you just landed Barack Obama a perfect stick to beat him with?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Well, this goes to the snob, snobbish issue, which is so he clearly did not tell the truth, that you don't necessarily go and accuse the person of -- of a person on a personal level.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "Is he a liar then?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "I am very happy to get behind any of these candidates because I want to have a unifying voice.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Were you disappointed that there is not a bona fide a Tea Party candidate left in the race?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I like Rick Santorum a lot, but I like Mitt Romney, I like Newt Gingrich, I like Ron Paul.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "Would that be a misreading?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "I think -- I think my opinions were fairly forthright throughout the debate and I felt quite honestly I was the perfect candidate for America.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Who do you most agree with?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well....", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "If you're so vehemently in the vanguard against ObamaCare, presumably Mitt Romney is the least of the four candidates that you would personally endorse, right?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "People have tried to portray you as a kind of ruthless money machine who some failed, some succeeded, you didn't care.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "What if Mitt Romney isn't the best person?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Well, there's no question but that a number of places where we went in and invested we were investing in an enterprise that was in trouble, that where the future was very much in doubt for it.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "To me the key question is do you know instinctively from your recollections how many of those companies that you went into would have failed anyway if you hadn't?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "It's actually the vice president landing.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "How funny is that?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "So let's keep the camera rolling, actually, because this interview has just been interrupted by Vice President Biden coming over our heads and wrecking his wife's interview.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "How funny is that?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "LINTON: -- is they don't have a tenable position.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Do you trust him?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "Not on this I don't.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Do you trust Ahmadinejad?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Well, I think he will be getting a certain amount of heat from some people because there's no doubt the sanctions are having a big effect.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "Do you still think it would have been a terrible error to do that?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "I think we need to ban gun control laws that keep people from being able to protect themselves.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "It seems to me that you're morally obtuse.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "You're an unbelievably stupid man, aren't you?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "No, my thought was this is how it ends, this is -- this is how I die, this can't be the way I die, this can't be the way my son dies.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Jamie, did you think that you were going to get out alive, or did you fear that everyone was going to die in there?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Well, I would take it one step further.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Why do so many Americans not feel angry enough to demand further gun control?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Well -- well, in -- you know, I take -- I take pause to that whole, you know, conjecture, again, of pulled out a gun and shot him.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "If we reversed this situation, and it was your brother who had been gunned down in exactly the same set of circumstances, and the worst that had happened, as far as his behavior, was that he had been followed, and he'd got into an altercation and he was unarmed -- he just had a bag of Skittles on him -- and a guy who was much older, who followed him in the street, pulled out a gun and shot him dead, would you not at the very least, if you're honest and candid about this, would you not have expected that person to at least be arrested, to at least perhaps face some kind of trial, where the full evidence could come out?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Well, he stopped someone from disarming him and shooting him.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "He did pull out a gun and shoot him, right?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "He had a permit to carry that gun.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "But he had the gun on him, right?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "The gun, I believe, was in his -- inside, tucked inside his pant waist...", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "But where was the gun?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "Well, he has taken control of his firearm.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "So he has pulled it out, and he has fired it?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "I'm not sure what can be done about it exactly.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "What can you really do about it?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "You know, it is a little bittersweet.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "How did you feel when you heard the news?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "I think that it's -- it's unnatural.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Do you think homosexuality is a sin?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "I'd sit down and I'd have a heart to heart with him, just like you would with your kids.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "What do you do if one of your six kids says, \"Dad, bad news, I'm gay\"?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "Well, I wouldn't say, \"That's great, son, as long as you're happy.\"", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "What would you say?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "I probably did, I probably did, if I -- if I remember.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Did you have wake up this morning and have a quick, you know?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "I think some people have more tolerance, you know, for smoking pot than others, and I know people who can take one hit and just go to sleep completely and other guys that can smoke a lot.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Do you take a lot of it?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "Now we can go to Colorado.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "You and Snoop go to Amsterdam, the Mecca of dope, really, and you both have a load of it and then write some music together?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Do you think the world is a more peaceful place now than it was when you first became Dalai Lama?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Well, I think there's hope.", "docId": "130105pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "How do you convince them to take your lead?", "qSentId": 524}]